https://carecenter-okc.org/privacypolicy/

Skip to content
ExpansionWe HealVictim ServicesSurvivor StoriesWe EducateEducation ProgramsAdult EducationChild EducationLicensingSupport UsDonateVolunteerBrave BallStand Up for KidsSarah’s ChallengeAbout UsWhat We DoStaff & BoardTour The CARE CenterNews and ResourcesContact
MenuExpansionWe HealVictim ServicesSurvivor StoriesWe EducateEducation ProgramsAdult EducationChild EducationLicensingSupport UsDonateVolunteerBrave BallStand Up for KidsSarah’s ChallengeAbout UsWhat We DoStaff & BoardTour The CARE CenterNews and ResourcesContact
Donate
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.carecenter-okc.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, registration forms, or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future with updates from The CARE Center. Registration FormsOn some pages in this site, you may be prompted to complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you regarding the reason you completed the form. For example, interest in volunteering or an education training require completion of an online registration form. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any of your personally identifiable information.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Links This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 405.236.2100 or via email at info@carecenter-okc.org.
Search for:
Recent Posts Mental Illness Awareness Week LGBTQIA+ Youth & Parent Resources Pool & Water Safety COVID-19 Safety Measures First Lady Joins CARE Center Mission to Help Abused KidsRecent CommentsArchivesOctober 2020June 2020May 2020April 2020March 2020November 2019September 2019June 2019May 2019April 2019March 2019January 2019December 2018September 2018August 2018April 2017CategoriesAdvocacyCOVID-19 ResourcesDigital ResourcesEducationKeeping your children safe at homeNational Child Abuse Prevention Month (NCAPM)NewsRecognizing and Reporting Child AbuseSexually appropriate behavior for every ageTips for surviving Social DistancingUncategorizedMetaLog inEntries feedComments feedWordPress.orgjoin our email listSign up to get updates on special events and more from The CARE Center!
Name Email
Sign Me Up
Contact us405.236.2100info@carecenter-okc.orgVisit Us1403 Ashton Place Oklahoma City, OK 73117CHILD ABUSE HOTLINE1.800.522.3511Follow Us
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Linkedin
© The CARE Center, a non-profit 501(c)(3) organizationPrivacy Policy
